Hey everybody, I'm Pat Dennis and in the next minute I'm going to show you how to set up Codex.
The first thing I do is I tell it what kind of work I do. This allows it to give me a personalized
experience. #2: there might be projects that I was working on and other productivity or
coding tools. I want to port those over into Codex with a click of a button. #3:
I'm going to set up my plugins. I'm going to allow Codex to build documents,
spreadsheets, presentations, use my browser, use my computer, give it access to my
calendar, email, my Slack, my Google Drive, so that when I talk to Codex it can
interact with all these different systems seamlessly. The new sidebar is clean
and ready for us to use and all the projects that we might have been working
on inside of Claude, for example, are ready for us here.
The next thing we can do is hit the ground running.
I'm going to ask Codex to get me ready for an upcoming meeting.
I'm going to have it search my Google Calendar, my Gmail,
my Slack, and have it produce a brief for me
so that I'm ready for my upcoming sales call.
That's the setup, fully connected context,
and a useful first workflow all in about 60 seconds.